{"data":[{"question":"Sun weather can always be depended on in southern countries.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Sun","b":"always","c":"on","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":"- Sun-> sunny","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"The man that wife and family are away seems very lonely.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"that","b":"and","c":"are","d":"seems","answer":"1","explain":"-That-> whose","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Each year more and more people try setting new and unusual records.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"more and more","b":"people","c":"setting","d":"unusual","answer":"3","explain":"- Setting-> to set","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Someone else put 49,999 dominoes in a line and knocking them all down.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"else","b":"dominoes","c":"in","d":"knocking","answer":"4","explain":"-Knocking-> knocked","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"The peel were actually 52 meters long.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"were","c":"actually","d":"long","answer":"2","explain":"- Were-> was","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Why did all the customers at the Red Lion have to pay of their beer that week?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"did","b":"at","c":"have to","d":"of","answer":"4","explain":"- Of->for","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"The heavy rain made it possible for us to have our picnic.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"heavy","b":"it","c":"possible","d":"to","answer":"3","explain":"- Possible-> impossible","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"If you make a five-days trip across the Atlantic Ocean, your ship enters a different time zone everyday.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"make","b":"five-days","c":"enters","d":"zone","answer":"2","explain":"- Five-days-> five-day","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"When he arrived at the furniture shop, they had been sold the table he wanted.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"at","b":"furniture","c":"had been sold","d":"wanted","answer":"3","explain":"- Had been sold-> had sold","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"May Day regularly is celebrated in many countries around the world.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"regularly","b":"celebrated","c":"in","d":"around","answer":"1","explain":"- Regularly is celebrated-> is regularly celebrated","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}